NEHA BHOLE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Toronto, ON | (647) 927-3237 | connect@nehabhole.com | LinkedIn | GitHub | Portfolio

SUMMARY

A Full Stack Developer who brings creativity and organizational skills to solve problems and write efficient, elegant code. I thrive on tackling new challenges and customizing solutions to fit the unique needs of each organization. Drawing on my 9 years of experience in pediatric behavioral therapy, I bring strong interpersonal, empathy, and leadership skills to every project.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript/ES6,

Python, SQL

Frameworks: Node.js, Express, React, Django,

Flask, Next.js

Databases: MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL,

SQLite

Tools: Git, GitHub, Heroku, Railway

Concepts: MVC & MVT Architecture, Web Scraping, Unit Testing, Authentication, REST

API

Other: Materialize, Bootstrap, Pure CSS, Mongoose, Pandas, SQLAlchemy, Beautiful Soup

PROJECTS

Chroma (ELC Hackathon) - Repo | Live

MongoDB | Express | Node.js | Express.js | React | Heroku

- An app designed to help people with color vision deficiency (CVD) better identify and understand the colors in makeup products.

Simon - Repo | Live Nov. 2023 - Present

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | GitHub Pages

- A web browser version of the classic game Simon deployed using GitHub Pages
- Used localStorage in the browser for data persistence and display user high score data

Resource Vault - Repo | Live

Nov. 2023 - Present

Mar. 2023 - Present

Node.js | Express | MongoDB Atlas | Railway | REST API

- A MEN full-stack application built using the MVC model with Google OAuth
- Developed a backend with navigation that responds to the login status of the user

Know Me - Repo | Live

Jan. 2023 - Present

Python | Django | PostgreSQL | Heroku

- A Python/Django application built using MVT model, with Django Authentication

Leaf It To Me Plant Shop - Repo | Live

Jan. 2023 - Present

Node.js | Express.js | React | MongoDB Atlas | Mongoose | Heroku

- A MERN full-stack e-commerce application built using MVC architecture, with JWT auth

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Web Designer/Content Creator

2018 - 2019

Herbiculture Inc.

Brampton, ON

- Improved online customer user experience by dramatic redesign of the website.
- Used a Wordpress template and customized it using HTML/CSS/JavaScript.
- Created product photographs and graphic content for website and social media marketing.

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

Primary Instructor Therapist

2020 - Present

Aim Autism Services

Brampton, ON

- Implemented solutions to increase data recording efficiency and effectively manage data.
- Used creative thinking to keep treatment plans more effective and relevant to the client's ongoing progress
- Managed 5 client teams by supervising team members, delegating tasks and conducting performance reviews.
- Boosted client retention by building rapport and providing personalized care based on each client's individual needs.
- Onboarded new team members by updating them on clients and training them in therapy techniques.
- Delivered Applied Behavioral Analysis (ABA) and Intensive Behavioral Intervention (IBI) therapy services to clients and conducted parent training during in-home sessions.
- Maintained open communication between team members and clients' families regarding clients' progress.

Instructor Therapist

2014 - 2020

Aim Autism Services

Brampton, ON

- Delivered ABA and IBI therapy services to clients and conducted parent training during in-home sessions.
- Strove to make treatment plans more effective and relevant to client's ongoing progress.
- Nominated for a leadership role and promoted to primary instructor therapist with more responsibilities.

EDUCATION

General Assembly, **Software Engineering Immersive**, University of Toronto, **Data Analytics Certificate** 2023

2021